{"questions":[{"question":"A software component is an architectural entity that","level":"medium","answers":[" encapsulates a subset of the system\u2019s functionality and\/or data"," restricts access to that subset via an explicitly defined interface","has explicitly defined dependencies on its required execution contex","all the answers are correc"],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"what is the correct order in git when we want to make changes to the code?","level":"easy","answers":[" git push ->git commit - >git pul","git push >git pull - >git commit","git pull >git commit - >git pus","git pull >git push - >git commit"],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"During the maintenance phase changes are made to the product, which is true?","level":"medium","answers":["As more changes are made, making the changes becomes easier","The original system documentation becomes more important and reliable","The product is getting further and further away from its original design","The original regression tests remain current"],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"Black Box tests are:","level":"medium","answers":[" Access to unit tests, can be applied both manually and automatically","A general approach to tests at all levels, while looking at the system code"," Access to functional system tests - mainly to test the logic of a system's behavior","There is no correct answer"],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"Among the following types of software testing, which test is suitable for the Beta version of software?","level":"hard","answers":["Functional Testing"," Performance Testing","Regression Testing"," User acceptance testing"],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"In order to examine the quality of the product of the software development process in the project compared to other projects in the organization in the same field (for example air traffic control systems or inventory management systems) we will measure:","level":"hard","answers":["the amount of faults discovered in the project during code development","the density of faults discovered in the code during development"," the density of faults discovered throughout the entire development process","the density of faults discovered by the customer during the first year of operation after the delivery of the project"],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"Requirements: You prepare the requirements document for the requested software for the client, and it requires that the system provide browsing between the various screens within half a second. How would you classify this requirement?","level":"hard","answers":["Functional requirement - the system is required to browse.","Non-functional requirement - availability - the system should browse in an available manner."," Non-functional requirement - reliability - the system should browse within half a second.","Non-functional requirement - performance - the system should browse within half a second."],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"Design\/Development: Can a Singleton instantiate and return more than one object?","level":"medium","answers":["No, can only return one object, that's the whole idea."," No, it does not create objects, only checks for their existence."," Yes, it can be defined that it will return a predetermined amount of objects.","No, it does not return objects, only an answer if they exist."],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"Which Design Pattern is used when a method returns one of several possible classes that share a common super class:","level":"medium","answers":["Observer Pattern","Template Pattern","Factory Pattern","All answers are correct"],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"Which type of models, model the operation of the system without reference to its implementation?","level":"medium","answers":["Computation Independent Model (CIM)"," Platform Independent Model (PIM)"," Platform Specific Models (PSM)","All the answers are correct"],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"When you need many other objects to receive an update when another object changes, you use:","level":"easy","answers":["Observer Pattern","Factory Pattern","Template Pattern","Model\u2013View\u2013Controller "],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"Implementation-Level artifacts can be:","level":"easy","answers":["Source code, Executable files, JSON files","Source code, Executable files, Java .class files","Executable files, JSON files, Java .class files","Source code, Java .class files, JSON files"],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"In what order is the emergency repair process performed?","level":"hard","answers":[" Change requests -> Modify source code -> Analyze source code -> Deliver modified system.","Analyze source code -> Modify source code -> Deliver modified system -> Change requests.","Change requests -> Analyze source code -> Modify source code -> Deliver modified system.","Modify source code -> Deliver modified system -> Analyze source code -> Change requests."],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"Which software development method is an incremental development so the transition from development to evolution is a seamless one:","level":"medium","answers":["DevOps deployment methodology","  Waterfall development method"," Rapid application development","Agile development methodology"],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"Agile Software Development is based on","level":"medium","answers":[" Incremental Development","Iterative Development","Linear Development","Both Incremental and Iterative Development"],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"Select the option that suits the Manifesto for Agile Software Development","level":"medium","answers":["Individuals and interactions","Working software","Customer collaboration","All of the mentioned"],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"How many phases are there in Scrum ?","level":"easy","answers":["Two","Three","Four","Scrum is an agile method which means it does not have phases"],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"Which of the following is not included in Architectural design decisions?","level":"easy","answers":["type of application","distribution of the system"," architectural styles","testing the system"],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"what\u2019s true about Inspections and testing ?","level":"easy","answers":[" Both should be used during the V & V process","Inspections and testing are complementary and not opposing verification techniques.","answer 1+2 are true","all the answers are wrong"],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"Automated test components is : ","level":"hard","answers":["A setup part, where you initialize the system with the test case, namely the inputs and expected outputs.","A call part, where you call the object or method to be tested. "," An assertion part where you compare the result of the call with the expected result. If the assertion evaluates to true, the test has been successful if false, then it has failed.","all answers are correct"],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"what are different types of review with different objectives?","level":"hard","answers":["Inspections for defect removal (product);","Reviews for progress assessment (product and process);","Quality reviews (product and standards).","all answers are true"],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"what direct Reviews Objectives include :","level":"hard","answers":["Detect errors","Product approval","a+b are true","Informal meeting for knowledge transfer"],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"what fault with Requirements can drive to :","level":"easy","answers":["Causes of Software Errors","Cause of error with what should the customer get"," a+b are true","all answers are wrong"],"team":"Lion","correct_ans":"3"}]}